pick34.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Statement - - - Pick34.com - Pick34.com - Success with Better Numbers

Your privacy is important to Pick34.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Pick34.com collects, and the ways in which Pick34.com uses that personal information.

Personal information collection  
Pick34.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * information about transactions carried out over this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to Pick34.com.

Using personal information  
Pick34.com may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where Pick34.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Pick34.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Securing your data  
Pick34.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Pick34.com will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

Cross-border data transfers  
Information that Pick34.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Pick34.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

Updating this statement  
Pick34.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

Other websites  
This website contains links to other websites.

Pick34.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Contact Pick34.com  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or [NAME'S] treatment of your personal information, please write by email to legal@Pick34.com.

This privacy statement is based on a precedent created by [EMPLOYMENTLAWCONTRACTS.CO.UK](http://www.employmentlawcontracts.co.uk/) and published by [FREENETLAW.COM](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).
